csupomona.edu 2012-12-30

# Privacy Statement | Cal Poly Pomona

Pursuant to California Government Code Section 11015.5, Cal Poly Pomona may collect personal information on some of its web pages. Specific web pages may have their own privacy notifications, with specific information. The information below pertains to all other web pages in the csupomona.edu domain.

## Gathering of information

Information may be gathered through web forms, which you fill out and submit, or through browser cookies that are saved on your computer by your web browser when you visit some of our pages.

## Types of information gathered

### Authentication with BroncoName and BroncoPassword

This information is gathered to insure that information that is only intended for you is not delivered to others.

### Personal information, including your private phone numbers and home address

According to State law, "'Electronically collected personal information' means any information that is maintained by an agency that identifies or describes an individual user, including, but not limited to, his or her name, social security number, physical description, home address, home telephone number, education, financial matters, medical or employment history, password, electronic mail address, and information that reveals any network location or identity, but excludes any information manually submitted to a state agency by a user, whether electronically or in written form, and information on or relating to individuals who are users serving in a business capacity, including, but not limited to, business owners, officers, or principals of that business."

Personal information may be entered in BroncoDirect, and may be requested by other web pages, for the business purposes of Cal Poly Pomona. This information is for the sole use of Cal Poly Pomona as a part of its business relationship with you. It is not distributed outside of Cal Poly Pomona, except as required by state law or court order, but it may be reused within the university.

### Browser cookies

Browser cookies are small pieces of information written to your computer by your web browser, at the instruction of a web page. Cal Poly Pomona uses browser cookies to tie together multiple pages of a form, to allow you to remain authenticated for a period of time after you log in, to remove that authentication if you should forget to log out, and to track cumulative use of our web pages by all visitors. No information from browser cookies that we produce can be read by entities outside of the csupomona.edu domain. No personal information is recorded in browser cookies other than encrypted session identifiers (which are meaningless except to the web application you logged in to), and all page use statistics are cumulative, and do not identify you (although such identification may be possible, especially if you use a computer belonging to Cal Poly Pomona). Some sites, including BroncoDirect and Identity Management Services, require the use of browser cookies. You will not be able to use these sites if you have disabled cookies in your web browser.

## The length of time that browser cookies remain on your computer

Browser cookies may remain for minutes, days, or weeks, depending on their use.

## Removal of personal information

You have the option of having your personal information discarded without reuse or distribution, by contacting the owner of the relevant web page. Please note that this may interrupt or even irrevocably terminate your business relationship with Cal Poly Pomona, possibly resulting in, among other things, the loss of enrollment, loss of admission, or inability to receive salary or other compensation, since specific personal information that Cal Poly Pomona stores may be necessary for the business relationship to continue.

## Limitations

Any information acquired by Cal Poly Pomona is subject to the limitations set forth in the [Information Practices Act of 1977](http://www.privacy.ca.gov/ipa.htm) (Title 1.8 (commencing with Section 1798) of Part 4 of Division 3 of the Civil Code).

## Redistribution

Cal Poly Pomona shall not distribute or sell any electronically collected personal information about users to any third party without the permission of the user.

## Exemption from the Public Records Act

Electronically collected personal information is exempt from requests made pursuant to the [California Public Records Act](http://www.leginfo.ca.gov/cgi-bin/displaycode?section=gov&group=06001-07000&file=6250-6270) (Chapter 3.5 (commencing with Section 6250) of Division 7 of Title 1).

## Records requests
